loansfinance.net 2018-12-01

# Privacy Policy | The latest global business, finance and economic news|loansfinance.net

**1\. Collection of Data**  
Personal information is collected only by third-party transaction entities necessary for any charges that may occur. We do not collect any personal identifiable information on this web site intentionally or unintentionally. As on many web sites, the web server may automatically receive general information that is contained in server log files, such as your IP address, and cookie information.  
**2\. Use of Data**  
General data may be used to customize and improve your user experience on this site. Efforts will be made to prevent your data being made available to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) your consent is obtained, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out for the sharing of data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires interaction with a third party, or is provided by a third party, such as an application service provider; (iv) pursuant to legal action or law enforcement; (v) it is found that your use of this site violates the site policy, terms of service, or other usage guidelines, or if it is deemed reasonably necessary by the site to protect the site’s legal rights and/or property; or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party, in which case that third party will be able to use the data in the same manner as set forth in this policy. In the event you choose to use links displayed on this web site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies published on those sites.  
**3\. Cookies**  
Like many web sites, this web site may set and uses cookies to enhance your user experience and for proper merchant tracking. Advertisements may display on this web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer; such cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the parties providing the advertisement. However, the parties providing the advertising do not have access to this site’s cookies. These parties usually use non-personally-identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to this site. You can visit the Network Advertising Initiative if you want to find out more information about this practice and to learn about your options.We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  
If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.  
**4\. Minors**  
You must be a legal adult, or acting legal entity in your jurisdiction to download and/or use any of the products offered on this site.  
**5\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
Changes may be made to this policy from time to time. You will be notified of substantial changes to this policy by the posting of a prominent announcement on the site.
